你在做什么？-我重新整理过冰箱
-What are you doing? -I reorganized the fridge.
最底下放肉跟奶制品
See? Bottom shelf,meats and dairy.
中间放水果蔬菜
Middle shelf,fruits and vegetables.
最上面放过期食物
And top shelf,expired products.
你做这个干嘛？
Why are you doing this?
因为我无聊到快抓狂了
Because I'm bored out of my mind.
我已经去过 银行、邮局、干洗店
I've already been to the bank,post office and dry cleaners.
老兄，你做完了我一周的工作
Dude,you just described seven days' worth of stuff.
你要放轻松一点
Spread it out a little.
难道你从来没失业过？
Haven't you ever been unemployed?
我不是失业 只是进修中（有安息之意）
I'm not unemployed. I'm on sabbatical.
少跟我传教
Hey,don't get religious on me,okay?
你应该练习放轻松
A guy in your position needs to be better at relaxing.
不然我们家怎么会有安乐椅？
That's why we have comfortable chairs.
过来…坐下
Here,sit down.
准备好没？仔细看了
Ready? Watch.
然后…真好
And then....
就光坐着？
-So,what? We just sit?
当然不是，不只是坐着
-Oh,no,no.We're not gonna just sit.
看好了
Watch.
我是钱德宾
-Hello,Chandler Bing.
宾先生，我爱你
-Hello,Mr. Bing.I love you.
不管你是谁，别再打了
All right,whoever this is,stop calling me!
你已经骚扰我半年 一点也不好笑
It's been 6 months! It's not funny!
宾先生，我看得到你
I can see you,Mr. Bing.
你穿新西装真性感
You look sexy in your new suit.
求你看在上帝的份上，别再骚扰我了
Leave me alone! For the love of God,leave me alone!
这只是周三的乐子
And that's Wednesday.
本集播出：“情比兄妹深”
The One with The lnappropriate Sister
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
告诉你们
Hey,you guys! Guess what?
英国人要打来啦？
The British are coming?
你的笑话真冷
Oh,you and your ways.
圣诞节快到了 我要负责去募捐
Since it's Christmas,I'm going to be collecting donations.
我已经拿到铃铛 过几天就能拿到募捐筒
I have my bell and later on I get my bucket.
我要散播欢乐给大家
I'll be spreading joy to the people.
去年散播的不够多
Last year I spread a little joy,but not enough.
今年一定要让全纽约 都感受到
So this year I'm doing the whole city.
我有个高中同学也做了这样的事
I knew a girl in high school who did that.
结果成了红人
She was very popular.
怪了，你说话的口气跟钱德越来越像
It's weird,you're starting to sound a lot like Chandler lately.
胡说八道
That is so not true.
菲比，你要去哪里摇铃？
So,Phoebe,where are you doing your bell-ringing?
我分到梅西百货旁当红位子
They gave me a great spot right by Macy's.
新人很少分到这位子
They never give a good spot to a rookie...
可是只有我会用25种语言 说圣诞快乐
...but I'm the only one who can say "Merry Christmas" in 25 languages.
我说谎的
I lied!
天啊，丹尼在那边，你们看
Oh,my God. Here's Danny.Just watch this.
看见没？还在假装对我没兴趣
See? Still pretending he's not interested.
他走过来了，大家装不认识他 忘记他是谁
He's coming over. Pretend we've forgotten who he is.
你们好 丹尼
-Hey,guys. -Hey,Danny.
丹尼
Oh,Danny! Hey!
丹尼，你认得瑞秋吧
You know Rachel.
她人很好，长得也不赖吧？
She's nice. She's not bad to look at,right?
谢了，莫妮卡
Thanks,Mon.
当然啦
Of course.
你要不要跟她约会？
Do you want to go out on a date with her?
莫妮卡
Monica
好啊，周五可以吗？
Absolutely. Is Friday okay?
非常好，她等不及要赴约
Friday is perfect. She can't wait.
约会时 我可以直接跟她说话吧？
On the date,I'll be able to talk to her directly?
周五见
See you Friday.
你搞什么啊？
Okay,what the hell was that?
算了，不用说了
You know what? Don't answer me.
我要跟丹尼约会咯
I have a date with Danny!
已经4点半，午休该结束了
All right,it's 4:30,I guess my lunch break is over.
你们等下要干嘛？
-What are you guys gonna do?
既然你要回去上班 我们大概一起打几个电话吧
-lf you're going back to work...I'll probably just hang out. You know,make some calls.
我怎么会落选？
How could I not get the part?
主角就是出身皇后区的 29岁意大利演员
The play was about a 29-year-old ltalian actor from Queens!
泰莉雅雪儿突然有空
Well,Talia Shire suddenly became available.
她是女人耶
She's a woman!
你要我说什么？ 人家就是有办法
What can I say? She nailed it!
好吧，还有什么戏份？
Is there anything else?
你一定又会拒绝… 同性恋A片？
You'll just say no again,but...gay porn?
佳节快乐
Happy holidays!
圣诞快乐（西班牙文）
Feliz Navidad!
嗨（法文），圣诞快乐
Allo and Merry Christmas!
谢谢你，祝你幸福
Oh,thank you,sir! Here's some joy.
我来看看你做得如何
-How's it going?
很顺利
-It's going okay.
那好，我顺便捐点钱
Good. Let me help you out.
谢谢
Oh,thanks!
新的鹿皮外套？好像很贵
Is that a new suede jacket? It looks really expensive.
是不便宜
Yeah. I guess.
你刚去做指甲？
Just get your nails done?
对，我只剩这些钱了
Yes,Phoebe,but this is all I have,okay?
谢啦，佳节快乐，祝你幸福
Thanks. Happy holidays! Here's your joy.
谢谢，佳节愉快
Thank you! Happy holidays and Wait.
等等，只能捐钱不能拿
-You can't take money out.
我跟你换零钱搭公车
-I'm making change for the bus.
拿零钱就好 其他钱是要救济穷人的
Can't you leave the dollar for the poor?
我就是穷人，而且还得搭公车
I'm poor. I gotta take the bus.
佳节愉快，可是你不能…
Okay,season's greetings and everything,but still
咬我啊，小妞
Bite me,blondie!
除了祝他幸福，我还要…
I'm going to give him something besides joy. Just
那个角色根本就是为我而写 结果我竟然落选
I can't believe I didn't get that part.
很遗憾
I'm sorry,man.
你知道该怎么做吗？
What you should do...
你要自己创造机会
...is make something happen for yourself.
例如写个戏剧或者电影剧本
You know,like write a play.Or a movie.
就像《心灵捕手》里的那两个角色
What about those Good Will Hunting guys?
罗斯，少作白日梦了
Be realistic,you know?
就算我写出剧本 哪有办法请到他们出演啊？
If I did write something...what are the chances I could get those guys to star in it?
有了，我可以自己主演
Wait a second. I could star in it!
也可以
Or that.
我不会写剧本
I can't write. I mean,
我是演员
I'm an actor.
我可以装成编剧
I could act like a writer. Here....
不过…什么也写不出来
But see? Nada.
我不像编剧一样有纪律
I don't have the discipline that it takes.
我办不到
I can't do it.
我可以帮你
I'll help you.
帮你订出时间表 盯着你乖乖照做
Yeah. I'll make up a schedule and make sure you stick to it.
我自己也有事做了
Plus,it'll give me something to do.
真的？你愿意帮我？
You'd do that for me? Thanks.
对 谢谢
Yes-Thanks
一开始慢慢来
We'll start slow.
今晚之前只要想好主角名字
All you have to come up with tonight is the name of your main character.
好了
-Done.
不可以是乔伊 不是
-And it can't be Joey.-It's not.
也不能是乔瑟夫
-Or Joseph.
你怎么啦？
What's up?
我刚看到丹尼跟女生搭地铁
I just saw Danny on the subway with a girl...
他还搂着她
...and he had his arm around her.
我真为你难过
Honey,I'm sorry.
你的确该难过，一切都要怪你
You should be. This is all your fault.
谁叫你插手我们的感情世界
You meddled in our relationship!
你们根本没在一起
You had no relationship!
不过我已经拟好计划 一切都按部就班进行中
But I was doing my thing and everything was going according to the plan!
拜托别再提你的什么计划
Oh,God,stop with the plan!
你看到他跟女生在一起又如何 他们不见得是情人
So what if you saw him with a girl?That doesn't mean anything.
你就快跟丹尼约会
You'll go out with Danny
到时你可以迷得他忘记地铁那个蠢妞
and be so charming he'll forget all about that stupid subway girl.
那女生的确很蠢
She was kind of stupid.
你说得对
You're right.
好，我就去约会
I'm just going to go on the date.
我会去赴约 这就是我的新计划
I'm just going to go on the date. That is the new plan.
快点
Hurry!
“多疑”怎么写？
-How do you spell "suspicious"?
干嘛？ 因为这个角色很“多疑”
-Why?I think this character is going to be suspicious about stuff.
太棒了！
Yes
钱德宾7分，钱德宾0分
Chandler Bing,seven! Chandler Bing,zero!
看你玩那个都快让我疯了
You're driving me crazy with that.
我不玩就是了
-I'll stop.
继续玩，碗拿远一点 连罗斯都投得进
-Don't stop.Move the bowl further away. Ross could make that shot.
真是逊毙了 不过至少你进了成人组
Well,you suck. But at least you suck at a man's game now.
要不要玩？
-Want to play?
我不能跟你玩 罗斯就快回来了
-I can't play games.Ross'll be home soon.
按照他的时间表 我今天应该写完5页
I have to write five pages to stick to his schedule.
你可以先玩30分钟 再继续用功到他回家
So play for 30 minutes,then write until he gets home.
好吧
All right.
不过规则应该更困难
But listen,what do you say we...crank it up a notch?
愿闻其详
I'm intrigued.
要先找到可燃性液体
All right. All we need is a little lighter fluid.
好，不过你小心点 我还想拿回房租订金
But be careful. I want our security deposit back.
我们之前发明铁锤标枪时 就已经拿不回来了
We said goodbye to that when we invented hammer darts.
你记得哪面墙壁没补过吗？
Do you even remember which part of the wall is not spackle?
记得，这里
Uh yeah right here
谢谢，佳节愉快
Thank you! Happy holiday.
小姐，那可是垃圾，不可以…
No,that's trash,young lady. You can't
别这样，小姐，她竟然捐垃圾
Stop that young lady! She donated trash!
募捐筒着火了，来人啊
The charity's on fire!
太好了，谢谢，我正需要
Help! Thank you. I need that!
那是什么鬼东西？
What is this?
现在才早上9点耶
It's 9:00 in the morning!
我看看，场景，房间 一名男子满脸狐疑地走进来
All right. "A room.A man enters. He looks suspicious."
就这样？
That's it?
乔伊，你今天应该写5页 还包括一个高潮
You're supposed to have five pages done by now...including an exciting incident.
这是什么？
What is all this?
大火球游戏规则
"The Official Rulebook of Fireball."
我们刚在玩这游戏
That's the game we played.
很好玩，道具就是一颗网球 一个碗、可燃液体
It's great. You take a tennis ball,a bowl and lighter
这对你的事业有帮助吗？
This is helping your career?
你是要当演员 不是发明危险游戏
You wanted to be an actor.Not the creator of "Crazy Lawsuit Game."
你说得对，我该工作了
You're right. I'll get back to work.
为你感到惭愧，你应该懂事点，乔伊应该要工作
Shame on you! You should know better! Joey needs to work.
振作点
Now come on.
不行，等你写完5页才还你
You can have this back when the five pages are done.
我今晚很开心
-I had a nice time tonight.
我也是
-So did l.
幸好莫妮卡约我们出来
I'm really glad Monica asked us out.
我很想请你进去
I'd love to ask you in,
不过我妹来住我家 她可能睡在沙发上了
but my sister's visiting.I think she's asleep on the couch.
你妹妹？睡在沙发上？
Your sister?Your sister's asleep on the couch?
我上次看到你们搭地铁 现在她还睡在你沙发上
I saw you with her on the subway and now she's asleep on the couch!
我猜就是你
-I thought I heard you.
太好了，你起床了
-Hey,great,you're up.
瑞秋，这是我妹妹克莉丝塔
Rachel,my sister Krista.
克莉丝塔，这是瑞秋 嗨
Krista，this is Rachel
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
你应该告诉我要带朋友回来 害我穿得邋里邋遢
I wish you'd warned me. I'd have fixed myself up.
有区别吗？
-Like it would help.
你真坏
-You are so bad.
你才是
-You are.
是你 是你
-You are. -You are!
-You are.-You are
是你
You are
你完蛋了
You are so dead.
我要教训你一顿
I'm gonna get you. Come here!
很高兴认识你
It's very nice to meet you.
没有人，没一个人尊重募捐筒
Nobody! Nobody respects the bucket!
大家都丢些莫名其妙的东西
You wouldn't believe what people put in here!
你觉得这像垃圾桶吗？
Does this look like a garbage can to you?
不像 像烟灰缸吗？
Does it look like an ashtray?
不像 像尿桶吗？
Does it look like a urinal?
菲比，你还要回去募捐吗？
-So you going back out there?
当然，不过我受够了
-Yeah,but I won't take any more crap.
再也不当募捐好好小姐
No more Mrs. Nice Bucket.
加油，你在街上流浪过，够悍
Good. You're tough. You lived on the street.
我要当回街霸菲比
I'll go back to being Street Phoebe.
不过也不能一模一样 街霸菲比不可能跟你们做朋友的
But not totally back. Street Phoebe wouldn't be friends with you guys.
可以问个问题吗？ 当然
Can I ask you guys something?
我没有兄弟，实在不了解
I don't have brothers,so I don't know,
你们会打来打去吗？
but did you guys wrestle?
当然会
-Oh,yeah.
常常
-All the time.
而且我从没输过
In fact,I was undefeated.
因为你以前200多磅
Well,you weighed 200 pounds.
不过我还是跟猫咪一样矫健
Still,I was quick as a cat.
我昨天碰到丹尼的妹妹
I met Danny's sister yesterday.
就是跟他一起搭地铁的那个
-That was the girl on the subway.
真的假的？
-You're kidding.
他们非常…会扭打
They were very,you know...wrestle-y.
这样正常吗？
But I guess that's normal?
我们现在不会这样了
We don't wrestle now.
自从我长大变壮后就不打了
Not since I got too strong for you.
长大变壮？ 对
Too strong for me?
你要比划一下吗？
You wanna go right now?
我可以立刻打败你，信不信？
I'll take you right now,buddy! You wanna go?
没问题
Oh,fine.
预备
Ready?
开始
Wrestle!
这个嘛…很好 谢谢你们帮了大忙
Okay,you know what?Actually,that helps a lot. Thanks.
赶快走，20分后就要开打了 乔伊，快点
Let's go! The puck drops in 20 minutes!
乔伊不能去
Joey's not going.
我还没写完5页
I didn't finish my five pages.
明天再写不就成了？
Finish them tomorrow.
因为他明天要修改昨天的5页
Tomorrow he's redoing yesterday's pages.
我昨天写的有待改进
Yesterday's pages did not reflect my best work.
别再逼他，让他透口气 搞不好会写得更好
Cut him some slack. If he relaxes,he'll get some work done.
他已经透够多气了 这都要感谢你跟大火球
I think he's been relaxing enough,thanks to you...and Fireball.
玩大火球可是很紧张 显然你没玩过
If you think Fireball's relaxing,you've never played.
你拼命压榨乔伊 是因为你自己没事做
You're doing this because you're bored.
又不是乔伊害你失业的
It's not his fault you're unemployed.
我不是失业，只是进修中
I am not unemployed. I'm on sabbatical!
你们别吵架
Guys,don't fight.
我之所以这么做 是因为我是乔伊的朋友
And I'm doing this because I am Joey's friend.
如果你也是他朋友 就该学学我
If you were a friend,you'd be doing the same.
当朋友就得这么混帐？
So being a friend means being a jerk?
要是真如你所说 你可真是我第一号好友
If it does,then you're an amazing friend of mine.
别吵了，大家玩场大火球决胜负
Let's settle this over a game of Fireball.
我去拆掉防火警铃
-I'll unhook the smoke detectors.
现在就做个了断
-Let's settle this right now.
好了，谁也不准去
There. Now no one's going to the game.
门票是我买的
-I paid for those!
才怪，你每次都说要付钱 却一次也没做过
-You said you would,but you didn't.
也对
Oh,yeah.
我们终于爬到山顶
We finally get to the top of the mountain...
结果这个笨蛋竟然忘了相机
...and airhead here forgets the camera.
我也发生过这种事情
The same thing happened to me one time.
你什么时候发生过？
When did that happen to you?
上次我们到公园慢跑 看到一只小鸟
Remember? We were jogging and saw that bird.
我刚想拍下来 发现竟然没带相机
I wanted to take a picture,but I didn't have my camera.
也对，不过追小贩可不算慢跑
Chasing the churro guy is not jogging.
超好吃，你一定要吃一口
Oh,this is so good. You have got to try it.
糟糕，裤子沾到了
-Damn. I got it on my pants.
我来擦
-Here,I'll get it.
最好上楼换件裤子 否则以后洗不掉
We better take them off or the stain will set.
而且我今晚约会还要穿
-I want to wear them tonight.
真好
-Oh,great.
再见，上帝呀
Okay,bye. Oh,my God!
不可思议
-That was unbelievable.
看吧，我早说过了
-See? I told you.
可怜的瑞秋
Yeah. Sorry.
我不相信他们是兄妹
I don't believe they're brother and sister.
他们是兄妹？
They're brother and sister?!
看来你得取消约会了
I guess you'll have to cancel your date.
而且还要打电话给他们老妈
And call their mother.
“非尿桶”
“我没有百货公司简介”
等一下，手张开给我检查
Wait a minute. Open your hand. Let me take a look.
两毛五、一毛、线头？不要
Quarter,dime. Lint? Not interested in that.
这是什么？加拿大硬币？滚
What's this? A Canadian coin?Get out of here!
不准在募捐筒旁边喝东西
No drinks near the bucket.
先放在那边才准捐款
Set it down there and then you can make a contribution.
少装一副可怜兮兮的样子
You can leave the "hurt bunny" look over there too.
嗨，鲍伯
Hi,Bob.
不是叫你滚了吗？
I thought I told you to get out of here!
菲比，我们接到投诉 所以要调你离开
Phoebe,we've been getting complaints.We're moving you to a less high-profile spot.
什么？
What？
以后这里由金杰负责
-Ginger's taking this corner.
这小妞才没这能耐
-That chick can't handle my corner.
你不走，我们就得赶你走
Look,either you leave or we remove you.
好
Fine.
提醒你一下，注意那个臭婆娘
I'll give you one pointer. Look out for that bitch.
瑞秋，不是约7点吗？
-I thought we said 7.
今天就算了
-You know what? Let's skip it.
什么？为什么？
What? Why?
你们兄妹似乎…非常要好
You and your sister seem to have a very special bond
太好了，又说这句话
Oh,great. That "special bond" again.
我跟我妹感情好 又是哪里让女人看不顺眼了？
Why do women have a problem with my being close to my sister?
听我说，我不知道事实真相 你有兄弟吗？
-I don't know,but -Do you have brothers?
没有，我有两个姐妹
No,I have two sisters.
其中一个很像男人婆
But one has a very masculine energy.
你们要好吗？
-Are you close?
没有，她们不是好人
-No. They're not very nice people.
我很喜欢你
I like you.
应该可以顺利交往
I think this could go somewhere.
我是跟家人感情深厚 别为了这个妨碍到咱俩
So I'm close to my family. Don't let it stand in our way.
我也不知道…
Well,I don't know....
如果你这么说的话… 丹尼快点，洗澡水快凉了
When you put it that way…Danny? Hurry up. The bath's getting cold.
怎么了？
What？
我先走了
I'll see you later.
路上有小孩在玩耍
There's some kids playing in the street.
你要不要去叫他们写作业 毁了他们的一天？
Want to go give them a project,ruin their day?
如果你手边有球 就可以插上剃刀
If they have a ball,you could stick razors in it...
教他们玩“杀人球”
...and teach them a new game: "Gonna-Need-Stitches Ball."
我整个早上都待在图书馆
Hey,guys! I was at the library.
已经写完今天的5页了
I already finished my five pages.
好，我们可以去看 昨晚的骑兵队比赛了
Now we can go to the Ranger game last night!
不行，门票给罗斯撕掉了
No,dude. Ross tore up the tickets.
没有让你分心的事情 就比较容易专心吧？
I guess without so many distractions it's easier for you to focus?
没人整天跟在你屁股后面 也比较得心应手吧？
Also without somebody breathing down your neck all the livelong day!
随便你们说什么，重要的是我写完了
The important thing is,I finished it.
而且写得还不错
And I think it's really good.
不过你们帮忙念台词 才是帮大忙
But it would help if I could hear it.
可不可以帮个忙？
Would you guys read it for me?
好吧 好
-Yeah,all right. -All right.
“一间普通的纽约公寓”
"It's a typical New York apartment.
“两个男人正在家里”，罗斯
Two guys are hanging out."
嗨
"Hey,man."
有什么事？
"What is up?"
昨天是我错了，对不起
"About yesterday. I was really wrong. I am sorry."
我才该道歉，我反应过头了
"No,it was me. I'm sorry. I overreacted."
或许我们都有错 反正我们都是为了朋友…
"Maybe it was both of us. But we had our best friend's inter
我们都是为了朋友好
But we had our best friend's interest at heart."
我更要说对不起
"Could I be more sorry?"
我才是该道歉的古生物学家
"l don't know. I am one sorry...polontologist."
乔伊，我们懂了
All right,Joey,we get it.
对不起 我也该道歉
-I'm sorry. -I'm sorry too.
你们要继续读下去 精采的才要上场，继续念
Keep reading. The good part's coming up.
对不起，钱德
"l am sorry,Chandler."
对不起，罗斯
"l am sorry,Ross."
“帅哥上场”
"A handsome man enters."
嗨！ 不知道你们在谈什么
"l don't know what you're talking about,
不过我要向你们两位道谢
but I'd like to thank you both.
你让我不放弃自己
You. You wouldn't let me give up on myself.
你，你与我一起创造了大火球
And you.You co-created Fireball."
“剧终”
"The End."
这就花了你一整天？
This took you all day?
没有，我只写了5分钟
No,this took five minutes.
其他时间都在写 “终极大火球”游戏规则
I spent the rest of the day coming up with new Ultimate Fireball!
场景在一般纽约公寓
It's a typical New York apartment.
屋内有两个女生 开始
Two girls are just hanging out. Go.
嗨，凯莉，你好吗？
-"Hi,how are you doing,Kelly?"
我很好
-"I'm doing just fine.
提芬妮，天呐 你今天好香
God,Tiffany,you smell so great."
我喷了新香水
"It's my new perfume.
你过来一点才闻得仔细
Why don't you come closer where you can really appreciate it?"
乔伊，你这大变态
-Joey,you are sick.
真恶心 我才不要念
-This is disgusting.I'm not reading this.
什么？等等，帅哥才刚要上场
Wait,wait,wait! The handsome man was about to enter!